### Contact

ccunurse20@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bradprior-22a44044 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals CCRN

#### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

# **Brad Prior**

RN at Kadlec Medical Center

West Richland, Washington

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Critical Care Nursing, Hospitals, Healthcare, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Washington State University.

## Experience

Kadlec Medical Center RN November 1999 - Present (20 years 8 months)

Emery Worldwide
Outbound Operations Manager
June 1983 - August 1990 (7 years 3 months)

### Education

Washington State University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1997 - 1999)